<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<doxygen xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="compound.xsd" version="1.8.16">
  <compounddef id="md__c_1__users__school__user__code__t_m_s-_dump__transport__management__system__w_p_f_packages__bb4bf1c016a2490d0cd8a96342590661" kind="page">
    <compoundname>md_C:_Users_School_User_Code_TMS-Dump_Transport_Management_System_WPF_packages_BouncyCastle.1.8.3.1_README</compoundname>
    <title>The Bouncy Castle Crypto Package For C Sharp</title>
    <briefdescription>
    </briefdescription>
    <detaileddescription>
<para>The Bouncy Castle Crypto package is a C# implementation of cryptographic algorithms and protocols, it was developed by the Legion of the Bouncy Castle, a registered Australian Charity, with a little help! The Legion, and the latest goings on with this package, can be found at <ulink url="http://www.bouncycastle.org">http://www.bouncycastle.org</ulink>. In addition to providing basic cryptography algorithms, the package also provides support for CMS, TSP, X.509 certificate generation and a variety of other standards such as OpenPGP.</para>
<para>The Legion also gratefully acknowledges the contributions made to this package by others (see <ulink url="http://www.bouncycastle.org/csharp/contributors.html">here</ulink> for the current list). If you would like to contribute to our efforts please feel free to get in touch with us or visit our <ulink url="https://www.bouncycastle.org/donate">donations page</ulink>, sponsor some specific work, or purchase a support contract through <ulink url="http://www.cryptoworkshop.com">Crypto Workshop</ulink>.</para>
<para>Except where otherwise stated, this software is distributed under a license based on the MIT X Consortium license. To view the license, <ulink url="http://www.bouncycastle.org/licence.html">see here</ulink>. The OpenPGP library also includes a modified BZIP2 library which is licensed under the <ulink url="http://www.apache.org/licenses/">Apache Software License, Version 2.0</ulink>.</para>
<para><bold>Note</bold>: this source tree is not the FIPS version of the APIs - if you are interested in our FIPS version please contact us directly at <ulink url="mailto:office@bouncycastle.org">office@bouncycastle.org</ulink>.</para>
<sect1 id="md__c_1__users__school__user__code__t_m_s-_dump__transport__management__system__w_p_f_packages__bb4bf1c016a2490d0cd8a96342590661_1autotoc_md1">
<title>Mailing Lists</title>
<para>For those who are interested, there are 2 mailing lists for participation in this project. To subscribe use the links below and include the word subscribe in the message body. (To unsubscribe, replace <bold>subscribe</bold> with <bold>unsubscribe</bold> in the message body)</para>
<para><itemizedlist>
<listitem><para><ulink url="mailto:announce-crypto-csharp-request@bouncycastle.org">announce-crypto-csharp-request@bouncycastle.org</ulink> <linebreak/>
 This mailing list is for new release announcements only, general subscribers cannot post to it.</para>
</listitem><listitem><para><ulink url="mailto:dev-crypto-csharp-request@bouncycastle.org">dev-crypto-csharp-request@bouncycastle.org</ulink> <linebreak/>
 This mailing list is for discussion of development of the package. This includes bugs, comments, requests for enhancements, questions about use or operation.</para>
</listitem></itemizedlist>
</para>
<para>**NOTE:**You need to be subscribed to send mail to the above mailing list.</para>
</sect1>
<sect1 id="md__c_1__users__school__user__code__t_m_s-_dump__transport__management__system__w_p_f_packages__bb4bf1c016a2490d0cd8a96342590661_1autotoc_md2">
<title>Feedback</title>
<para>If you want to provide feedback directly to the members of <bold>The Legion</bold> then please use <ulink url="mailto:feedback-crypto@bouncycastle.org">feedback-crypto@bouncycastle.org</ulink>, if you want to help this project survive please consider <ulink url="https://www.bouncycastle.org/donate">donating</ulink>.</para>
<para>For bug reporting/requests you can report issues here on github, via feedback-crypto if required, and we also have a <ulink url="http://www.bouncycastle.org/jira">Jira issue tracker</ulink>. We will accept pull requests based on this repository as well.</para>
</sect1>
<sect1 id="md__c_1__users__school__user__code__t_m_s-_dump__transport__management__system__w_p_f_packages__bb4bf1c016a2490d0cd8a96342590661_1autotoc_md3">
<title>Finally</title>
<para>Enjoy! </para>
</sect1>
    </detaileddescription>
  </compounddef>
</doxygen>
